[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
and hello everyone good evening who the vibration of the
а всем привет добрый вечер кто вибрация
stage is rightfully you so about the port
сцены можно по праву ты так про порту
ben exactly fell into the frame
бен точно попадал так в рамочку
and side is nothing to worry about
и сбоку ничего страшного
and delivery plus and who is here  everything hovers with a man,
а и поставкой плюс и кто тут у мужчины
it’s just that his
все витает это просто такие спадает
hearing subsides and moves the adapter crushes in
слуха и двигается adapter раздавится в
stock who to achieve in stock with a horse with
запасти кто добиться в запасе лошадкой
boobs 3 then so that we lyudmila
сиськами 3 потом чтобы мы людмилы там
read there go more expressions were with
читала идти больше выражения были with
primary key at a cool moment of his
primary key в прикольный момент его
delivery was and yes today we have
сдачи был и да сегодня сегодня у нас
adoptive darren so  since last night
приемный даррен так с вчерашней ночи
you can smell your kid in the sky and it’s great
вы чуют и your kid небе и здорово
for a beer puppy at a personal meeting and catch
на пивную щенок личному сходе и половить
quilted jackets at the cana with a
у каны [__]
tuned firewire com ukraine rima
настроенным firewire ком украина рима
obviously in a shirt not
гланое в рубахе не
water there they will say apolitical
воды там будут рассказывают аполитична
so there was a bunch of all sorts of combed to
так еще там была куча всякой чёсана to
america
america
and
and
shares chirkova black apple and  to the idol
shares chirkova black apple и к идолу
it is logical yarmola of ukraine to light
логично ярмола украины на световые
rhinitis yes we mean
ринита да мы разумеем еще
let's also say give the country from solidarity for
скажем дайте краины из солидарности для
ukraine i saw and voice and all i posted a
украины видывал и голос и all i posted a
and politician  and the atelier, let’s say, consolidation of the
и политика ателье скажем консолидация
retinue of navkolo ukraine, she
свиту навколо украины она читку
shows the reading, russia and belarus, were
показывает россия и беларусь
overwhelmed with
завалены была допущена этой позорной
samples of this shameful brush, and ukraine helped the water of
кисти пробники а украина помогла вода
them, I’ve been enjoying so far
них я вот наслаждался до сих не telegram
yakov
призрака так дай-ка я зайду яков
blazes
полыхает
so she’s on the right the farther he plays
так уж она справа чем дальше он играет
on the yard aren’t you so much better at this
на дворик ли ты не так уж лучше в этом
I’ll bite you 1
перегрызу тебе 1
so pissed 90 a lot of dan I won’t be alive
так обоссал 90 много дэну не буду жив я
there I instructed the time codes so there you need a
там тайм-коды по наставлял так там нужно
long time
давно
pier 3 points you are so andrei covenants
пирс 3 балла ты так андрей заветов
dubar  Bishop not just buildings of gardens and a
дубарь бишопу не просто построек садов и
couple of carts so it would
пару карки так бы
n’t be theirs, but in the darkorange elevator,
его не их а в лифте
get
darkorange
two higher for a long time didn’t bach you us
вали два выше давно не бачила вас нас
three filthy didn’t give much for the sake of sperm the
три поганый мало давала ради сперма
death of wine, but they
гибель вина а
planned there you have three pandas
планировали вот там у вас нас три панды
stitches for a long time didn’t bachila us because of the
швы давно не бачилы нас проходит ибо
members  we charge with positive I’ll write this
членов мы заряжаем позитивом напишу это
fur coat in 3d worlds than and cinema and can
шубина в 3d миры чем и и кино и может
change so
изменить так то
it’s you filthy we demand with
это вот у вас поганый нас требовать
tassels bought it takes away and always
кисточками накупила забирает и всегда
think it strengthens and  a brush and our
думаем укрепляет и кисточку и нашу
loggia, that is, it’s so and that you have plans for a
лоджии то есть он так и что вас планы на
car and, on the other hand, you’ll find it on you at a time,
авто и зато еще вина это вы за раз найду
well, we can’t from the elements
бы на тебе ну от мы не может от стихии
such to for 1 group, well, today you and the view of
такая к за 1 группы ну ты сегодня и вид
your godfather on the jet on painted
вашего пахану на струю on крашеный
will become  well, yes, there, to press down the dyed one,
станут ну да там на придавить крашеный
the krasin became a Ukrainian and the
стал украинцем красин и станы москалям
peaks of the Muscovites will become, but the look of your good
вершины станут а вот вид вашего хорошего
on this date impudently loaded us three
на по этой даты нахальным нас три
from the sedan in the entrance as
зарядил из у седана в подъезде так
positive as the smaller good pipes there
позитивом как меньших добрый трубы там
100 hryvnias about the movie
100 гривен про кино
firefighters on the streets there are sellers not in the
пожарные на стритам есть продавцы не
store  the poor and the soldier, and so so so
магазине бедняком и солдат и так так так
wines of latitude that we always have this with a kitchen
вин широты что мы всегда это с кухонным
on the island, the law is a folding drill, we will
на остров закон откидным бур будут от
always have a positive mood from the noise, we would have a
шума всегда позитивным настроем у нас бы
national 15 let’s say we Ukrainians
до национальный 15 скажем мы украинцы
organize a good mood from the car
организовывать от машины хороший настрой
15 a festive thief just what you want it
15 праздничный вора как раз и хочешь
to be before  than the darkness of her batteries razin
чтобы было прежде чем тьму ней аккумы
and chop out until the evening the
разина и рубить из до вечера звену
filthy link us three wines yes but
поганый нас три вина да но
scary cvh klm we are the fault of the nest and light
страшно cvh клм мы по вине nest и светла
and
так и
cheap route systems, then maybe even
дешевого маршруту системах то может даже
you will fall out and  With a good island
вам выпадет из хорошим острова
it was cool to iron and the ensign is more
было круто по утюжит и прапорщик больше
twisted and this one can move and
крутишь и данный можете переехать и пути
you’re already on the way, but the question is, otherwise the doctors
уже ты ну а вопросу а то врачи
served food to the lawyer nothing of their own
еду подавались адвоката ничего свои
53000 guys will jump out where the stream will go
53000 парни выскочат куда двинется стрим
and then succumb to the lawyer on your
а потом поддаетесь адвоката на ваш
lawyer rolled out and so God forbid he
адвоката раскатал и так что дай боже он
and everyone knows the mana on these
и все знают маны на этих
adequate chest and
адекватный ты за беспокойство грудь и
stretch the moment to climb out
потянитесь момент вылазить
after the keyword there the Anglo-Saxons
после ключевого слова там англосаксы
flexible understand about the bomb burst so
гибкий понимаешь о ворвалась бомба так
thinks today it will be fun our
думает сегодня будет весело наши дилеры
serval dealers vidos on the finger the little more
сервала видос на пальчик the little еще
to give and we seem not to understand
давать и нам это кажущийся не разбирать
this expose thinkin'  Fathers
этом выставляете thinkin' у батюшек
Secret Jay have a pleasant spirit and also kinds of
секрете джея приятное духа и тоже видов
me.
я . еще
and the dirt is not for you to lose weight further,
а грязь вам худеть дальше не строчка
hahah,
хахах на
it’s at a thin point of colors people, but people
это на худе красок люди но люди
make up hoodies,
накрасить худи
I’m kuzan crying by choosing yak orestovich spill places,
я кузану плач выбором як орестович места
damn it, I’m sticks on the shaft and
разлива блин вот я стики на вале и
understood 2, you couldn’t teeth, you’re nothing
понимали 2 не смогла зубы ты ничего
shorter than the night owl’s time, orestovich
короче ночных у совы время орестович
places for evil  his
места во зло его
type of picard sources dared where
типа пикар источники смел где
you tanci drink lol and
вы tanci напитка лол и
inside would say to sew and under
внутри бы высказала шить и под
arrest that you would recognize knots in places
арестованы что вы бы местами узлы узнает
orestovich you are at the
орестович вы на минималка я
minimum wage I will mix a tank of fables with a lawyer completely
смешаю бачек басен с юристом полностью
super three great now you
супер три великие сейчас вы зазвучать в
would like to sound in the chat roulette because otherwise
чат рулете хотелось бы поскольку а то
100 damn for your content it was
чтобы 100 дякую за ваш контент блин было
so straight virat that it gets anomalous
так прям вираты что попадает аномальная
on Mayakovskaya concrete often joking there
на маяковской конкретного часто шуя там
already in such Dan’s so vaguely for her
уже в таких у дэна так туманно ей
villa often and leaving
вильной часто и уход
besides
помимо и
and already spoke with the godfather for the lads that to
и так говорил с кумой для хлопцы что
bend with two our good
прогнуться с при двое наш хороший нас
three of us look  our people are on the other
три выглядят наши люди на помещаете иные
side of life lads and I know the normal functions
жизни хлопцы и я знаю нормальных функций
will try them on the way to sound like and
попытается их на пути на звучать как и
through the east not march
через восточную не марта
the ok
the ok
there for next to the positive  ohm and reasons,
там за рядом со позитивом и и причинам
so who are you a template,
взгляду так кто вы шаблон
but with this to
а вот с этим
say to fight back everyone who is shenno, I
сказать отбиться всех кто шенно я
switched to Ukrainian in the dose, put
перешел в досе на украинскую поставьте
plus who knows something stock and minus the
плюс кто знает что-то запас а минус
pants are aware that this is a stock and at a time we
штаны в курсе что это запас и за раз мы
will tell you about this dog
расскажем про этого пса
cons that
минусы что
no, angleless o.s.
нет , безуглова о.с.
centuries of peeling and heard both us and cleave us and the
веков корки и слышал и нам и клайв нам и
keyboard player st and sang and 5 and in our
клавишник ул и напевал и 5 и в наших
merits our merits are debra faces up so
заслуг наши заслуги дебра лица up so
when in a month you are in Ukrainian so it
when за месяц вы в украинскую так это
chases the former Ukrainian so bad in a month
гоняется за месяц бывшим украинскую
tx y ps the Russian pass will so
так то плохо tx у ps российский пас так
soften and  knead the ukrainian yet you
смягчит и замесить украинскую еще вам
ukrainians ukraine infecting deductions and
украинцам украине заражая вычеты и
agreed ukraine therefore i seem .
столковались украине поэтому я кажусь .
dasis packs Ukrainian
dasis пакуется украинскую
Grigorovich, we are every seams of
григорович нас каждый швы
luminesce of those abs you will justify, I don’t think
luminesce тех abs оправдаешь не думаю
that there is something, let’s say the dog has more air there, there is
что что то есть скажем у пса там воздух
more cranium and redness to a
больше там черепная коробка и краснота к
person Ukraine, they say, but we can’t
человека украина мол на но не можем же
look like smearing flies that you and strong came
вид мазать мух тот вас да сильный пришел
to Ukrainian comes, and therefore  that
на украинскую приходит а потому что
soon nights and in the yards there will be a lot of
скоро nights и в дворах будут вас куча
you, you are in favor of giving a Russian
ты за то чтобы дать российском
type of arch, I am writing to release one everything in the cheat of
типа арк пишу выпускать одну все в чите
clinics, they arrived to you careless Ukraine,
клиник прибыли вам беспечном украине
published in Ukraine, or else, let's
издавали по украине а то а и давайте
start 100, finally, a
начинаем 100 ваще
collage on the euro tower, even straighten the fate of the
коллаж на евро башни судьбу расправьте
culture of the state of emergency, I'm here  x plus cheekbones and
даже культуре чп я вот х плюс скулы и
such a cheng whale sharks people can
таких чэн кит акулы люди может биты
send bits for the joy of their principle a
отправил за радость своих принципе
man and doctors are not
мужчина и врачи не
from defense but there is political chaos Lois
от обороны но там политический хаос лоис
and
и
fang already turned out there the nose did not have time
клыка уж вышло там носа не успевала
to speak and whom the Seim of Mariupol
языку и кого там сейм мариупольского
steel
сталь
on an ingot of the body gamma globe their
на слитком тела гамму глобус ихняя
disqualification and
дисквалификации а
people, let’s say, there were also notes, but you didn’t
люди скажем набралось и заметок а вы не
put Taraz on a shawl, maybe you
ставила на шальке таразе можливо вы
are good at the topic, I’m cavanova in the rotation contest,
хороши в тему я cavanova в конкурсе
so Alla will remain silent  and you can say that
вращения так алла промолчит а можно вот
he’s
его
disqualified, you’ll say dragging you can
дисквалификации скажешь тащу ты маешь
say vessels at a time you start him and
сказать сосуды за раз ты ему старты и
steps your both temples for growth and looking for a
шаги твоим оба вискам за ростом ищет и
mouthpiece at a time millions of
рупор за раз накидываться миллионы
millions of people in carved lands and the
миллионы людей в резных краина так и
toilet was I want to show the USA grow
унитазу было я хочу сша растут показать
and they 2 the same i  wear towers, but in
и они 2 the same i wear башни а вот в
reserve, I looked at
запасе я вот глянув
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
azovstal pass and at
азовсталь пройти а у
wrote
писал
fragments from hold you tight to the sea q there
осколки из hold you tight морю q там
Azovstal primal
азовсталь праймал
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
he and who is said there is true
он и кто там говорится там правда
politics and so songs are sports and all is
политику и так песни спорт а все брехня
nonsense is politics  oh elite, you go on
то политика об элитка ты выходишь на
stage, you have to show up millions millions of
сцену надо вот являться мильоны миллионы
great people to lay gerds at a time you
людей великих заложить герды за раз
make costumes so big and you can
маешь костюмы так велико и ты можешь
get the results of everyone there good dain so I
результаты всех там добрый даин так я
'm glad you richer there will pat it
рад вас богаче там похлопает это
over and you can bring the landing or
обдумать а можешь донести и десант или
water to the tour was and that  still few
воды в тур был и то еще мало зубы-то
prominent teeth were taken into account on you, everything is still in
видных учитывала на тебя вся еще в
principle prominent, Ukraine was taken into account and here
принципе видных учитывала украина и вот
I am to x plus there in what come take my
я к х плюс там в чем come take my
vodka and people are ready to put five hundred
водку и люди готовы поставить пятистам
direct not so much t  the price of Belsky
прямого не так куча там цена бельских не
knowledge is not there in history, it will be possible to
там знания в истории можно будет
sum up the
итоги
statutes of tc on the stake of your own and those if
уставы tc на кон своих своих и тех если
yes, what kind of black paper was it and
да это вы какая была черную бумагу и
work not in rubles, so put a plus
труди не в рублях так поставьте плюс
sharp, but the view is about by the time tadic and at a
острым а вот вид о к моменту тадич и за
time we are faithful to him and  clapped I don’t respect
раз мы ему верна и захлопала не уважаю
yet the collage of the gums of the soul of a cool puppy
еще коллаж десны души крутых щенок
can know on the museum charge, then
может знать на и музейному заряде то
someone to throw what master and vice
кто-то так закинуть какие мастер с вице
was even the same cool
было даже ту же круто
so
так
after Katrina a bunch of
после катрины кучу
streams growing fakes on narrow ones and
стриме вырастающие фейки на узких и
you can two of this yourself russian and on the flag
можно два этой себе russian и на флаге
on  and the Russian lightning
на и российском молнию орестович актара
orestovich aktara you are playing the game andrey ass of ukraine
вы проходит игру андрей попками украины
in ukraine and ukrainian so
в украине и украинский так что
bakanov of a person says ukrainian
баканов человека говорит украинскую
arrested his canons not well damn it
арестован свои каноны не ну блин уж это
how can such a rumor of labor and rights
как можно таких слуха труда и права
take your tower forever there was a tile and
take your башня завжды было плитку и
today the tac snail is on the side of good
сегодня цап улитка на сторону добра
if  west at the euro boccioni west at the
если запад у на евро боччони запад на
post office azovstal cutout
почту азовсталь вырез
and let's succumb I want to go to the place you
и давайте поддаемся хочу до места вас
daikin we plunge into the don was
daikin окунаемся дону был
in berlin delusions continue our two
в берлине брени продолжают наши две
harnesses and this denunciation right up to the light  stu
жгуты и донос этот аж до световой
grammar stu court azusa and mariupol
грамматика стью суд азуса и мариуполь
[music]
[музыка]
straightens already cool so people go out
расправляет уже круто так люди выходят
poor people 2 linds and wear a massage so
люди бедные 2 линд и носить массаж так
here whales of the metro badal she can stand
тут киты метро badal ей про могут стоять
Mariupol residents so that at each
мариупольцев надо так чтобы у каждого
passage there are bald hallways into it mariupol
прохода прихожие в него лысых мариуполь
site of mariupol residents  so the
сайт мариупольцев мариуполь так
journalists, yes, and filmed a video on the firewood of
журналисты да и снимала видео на дрова
others soaked, he will show people to help the
других промок он и покажет люди помочь
language of Mariupol people maritime from schwing
язык мариупольцев maritime с от schwing
to file in the masses and even a pear cool ios I
подать в массах и даже груша круто ios я
want to show it is difficult to see from as much as
хочу показала трудно виду от аж на
Socrates of the Russian Federation there Azov Mariupol
сократа рф там азову мариуполе
1 officer of his cooling caviar speed sounds of a
1 офицер его остывания икра speed звуки
bombard  they are
бомбарду они
in the army
в армии
country mom mom
стране мама маму
efforts of
старания
this
этой
band
полосы
[music]
[музыка]
wash down and not mom cola cleavage hordes
запиваем и не мама колы сколу полчища
why you and your rida
почему ты и твои рида
syllable
слог
and the one who knows the
а тот кто знает
song
песня
with headphones euro the goddess is perceived
с наушники евро богиня воспринимается
completely with less nunish the song and sounds of the
совсем при меньшем нуниш песня и звуки
bombardo want to take the and say
бомбарду want to take the и скажем
a  the song is also a monastery and culture so you are
а песня тоже монастырь и культуру так вы
on the songs of the Ukrainian direct floor above the
на песнях украинской прямой этаж выше
choice and we do not know her fishing moon she
выбор и мы не знаем ее рыбачий луна она
has already begun to drink and jacket  q2 then she became in
уже стала пить и куртку q2 то она стала
time for ukraine, I think
успеваете украине я думаю еще же
she also studied clips of novelty and ruined the clip
обучалась клипы новизне и сгубило клип
on the basis of this
на основанию это
and let's rise above it for hours the syrup
и давайте поднимемся над им часам сироп
is
это у
taken from us and our less
брать и наших меньше
in the arch 100 are not in power
в арку 100 не властны вси беру
the team is shorter than omsk novosibirsk shake of
команда короче омска новосибирска шейк
eight hundred and the strength of poplar goods is a good
восьмиста и силах товар тополя хороший
contest for me a pudovo this is novosibirsk for the
конкурс мне пудово это новосибирск на
right [ __ ] here he will give this we
правильному шлюху вот он этом даст мы
revered straight and
почитаемого прям и
called names
обзывалась
like the market at a time
как рынке за раз я открыл грамм нэйша
performed in the
15 оправдаться сегодня уже выполнены в
boom competition for beautiful
соберу бум конкурс по прекрасно по
embellishment oohmur in short three teams over the
прикрас охмурил короче три команды за
years well, you weren’t beautiful you were my
годы ну по вы не была прекрасна ты мой
new porsche in russia
новый porsche в россии конкурса по
embellishment competition they came to
прикрас они могил реки пришел в
novosibirsk at
новосибирск у
jacques means there were participants in
жака значит был участники севастополя
sevastopol omsk novosibirsk then some used
омска новосибирска то одни использовали
tile film others
плитку пленку другие искусственные живые
artificial flowers  and xml reward the
на могиле на лотти прикрас и xml награ
people of all whom his claim sailor the
народ весь кого его исковом моряка
Novosibirsk team forgot the false
новосибирская команда забыла фальшь
grave for urns about friendly couples but
могилу для урн о дружные пары а при
could remember as a team and to the redbo chela of the
могла помнить как команда и к redbo чела
month for the living one
месяца для живых одно
single river video of Alonso tires everything is
одну речных видео алонсо шины все
revealed in it and the barrel of the lesson was
выявляется в нем и дуло уроку так
conducted a similar competition I  here, under the
проводили схожий конкурс я у тут под
goose, he went to a lesson, so he was from the
гусиный шел он уроку так в мир был из
sea by mistake sleeping at digging graves,
моря по ошибке сном у выкапыванию могил
I don’t know what to cut in their heads is
я не знаю что рубиться в головах их
shorter russian of this type of
короче russian такого типа
pericle dates your where a lot of rock in 400
перикла даты ваш куда много рок в 400
baiting 2020 pasha in the nose the tag came
травля 2020 паша в носу бирку пришли
smaga not at the seam  there are a lot of digging
смага не по шву таких много выкапывания
graves, because they took them and the fate will become a
могил ведь их взял и участь станете
funeral stuffed in the region of Russia, and so
похорон набивных регионе россии и так
on, shorter than a clown, really clowns of
дальше короче клоуна реально клоуны
this kind, in principle,
такого в принципе
studios for them not in spending in Ukraine, such a
студии на их не в траты в украине такую
normal competition, so we, in principle, are in favor of
нормальный конкурс итак мы в принципе за
having a dome in Russia and more graves in
то чтобы в россии купол и больше могил в
Russia  to get higher graves as we want it
россии к получишь выше могилы как хотим
stops than put it very much plus why
прекращает чем очень поставьте плюс че
do you respect that there are more graves in russia
вы уважаете что больше могил в россии
equipment for us and cons by the way gas is
технику для нас а минусы кстати газ
sad about two bodies and / eat  it’s
печально о два тела и / ему
concrete in russia that she’s about to
именно в россии она и про
get inspired until
газует вдохновись до
he’s
он
from the explosion of the [ __ ] experience la yes,
от взрыва [__] опыту la да
it means more graves in long
значит больше могил на руси длинной
russia to
россии
crash
грохнуться
and corrals they wrote down
и загонов они записала
so he and sharif and so
так он и шариф и так
about the east of existence more in russia it’s
о востоке бытования большему на руси это
kind to him right cool scarecrow and  i’m
добрая на ему верна круто пугало и я
neutral and so they’ll vote,
нейтральные и так проголосует выслали
let’s say a little bit like that and basenko in
скажем чуть а почуття так и басенко в
russia contests good high wines from
россии конкурсы хороший хай вин из
turn around there a flower grave digger and
обернуться там цветку копатель могил и
like a joke such an occasion fashionable short
типа шутка такой повод модную короче
good skill them 3 vrazhin emotions and we
добрый навык им 3 вражин эмоции и примем
’ll accept like I bet as we go further
like ставлю так как едем далее
and there’s no
и нет то у
I didn’t take
я не брал
such a theme as a Romanesque theme,
торжествуют нак романскую такую тему так
so they also have a dead zombie grandmother, so with
у них и так же мертва бабка зомби так
references and daughter
справками и дочь
, do you know the cyst, you love adequate
же знаете ли киста любишь адекватные
Russians, it amazed the sablin symbol, well, death,
россиян изумило саблин символ ну смерти
so it can die soon with us, like
так она может у нас скоро сдохну типа
this with russian lyrics, we have a
такой вот с russian lyrics у нас там
sum there  data of the vessel and pop it keys
сумма данных судна и суют она keys
small stars with a letter and then for
маленькие звезды с буквы и зато за
handing out
раздаем
with a big try succumb
с большим попробуем поддавайтесь
zara
zara
floor
пол
about pancake grandma to super i canadian
о блин бабкой к супер я канадка
blocks serve as a pref  eating, well,
блоки служить приведя ну
baby b
малыш b
they are
им
very good, she is a grandmother, it becomes a little
очень хорошо она бабка это стать мало
go by the
идите по
sound, pointy, and debility panties,
звуку заостренные таки и штанишках
that’s all of Russia, yes, they’re just a grandmother there,
вот и вся россия да они просто бабка там
background and cops, people began to
предысторию и копы люди стали нужно
turn on, we can and I don’t know, I still want to
включить можем и не знаю еще хочется
seem like a grandmother to jumped out with a
кажется то бабкой к выскочила с
Russian ensign  damask gifs to
российским прапором дамасская гифки к
trains through then
поездами через то
if it is written they say you can’t invent a sword like
если пишется мол не придумаешь меч как
it’s russia on your head it seems that you
это же россия на голове кажется что не
can’t provide it for forever 6
обеспечены можно будет его на завжды 6
come up with rubles we have left destroyed
придумать рублей нам осталось разрушил
so my legs are
так мне штанины
straight really campitello stalin
прям реально кампителло сталина
here’s a drop of monad we’ll try it with belle
вот капля монада это попробуем с белль
[ __ ]
shit
he was
он был
she 1006
она 1006
yes to me and the casting
да мне-то и кастинг
clouding of the place nova
помутнение места nova
I at once with the bulba shown
я разом с bulba shown
are somehow twisted
так-то перекручены
Zhirinovsky going to we can be
жириновский перейдя на мы можем будем
so ok the window to the dogs already showed ok and
так окей окну собакам уже показывал ok и
let's go with rob
давайте с робом
, in the heading of the angle bases today we have
, в рубрике базах угла раз сегодня у нас
both healing  steam skating rink mov
и врачеванием и с катком пары мову
ukraine and whiners on his tower alupka
украины и нытики на его башне алупке
mental in the light and
ментальную в свете и
behind the houses such food
за дома такие питания
you around the corner and according to him who has a mouth
тебя за угла а по его кому рот не веков
like ukrainian  and minced meat performed on and
вроде украина фарша выступала на и
they cut them in who represented ours
врубать они их кто представлял нашу
kept
держал
write in the comments to the wild kind ukraine
напишите в комментах дикому роде украина
minced meat took your mocha right now it’s not theirs and
фарша взял щас your mocha не их-то и
imagined something wrong maybe tdi exit
представлял то не так может выхода tdi
TV set can exit then teki wo kann auto
телик может выхода то teki wo kann авто
can you and your tone write your own  versions
может ты и твой тон напишите свои версии
so heading without google here and we start
так рубрика без гугла тут а мы начинаем
and booze Wikipedia rubber torture there
и бухлом википедию резины пытаем там
we find out their
узнаём их
versions
версии
and
а
throwing a rosary went
выбросом четки пошли
private well at the university I would find it in
частный ну-ка в универе бы так найду в
honor of a slave like be creative
честь от раба типа будь креативным
try to go there to the truth this
пробовать там хода до правда у этого
cemetery of Tomsk district was for  I’ll figure it out,
кладбища томска уезда был за разгадаю
and the
а
eyes of the skin pack,
глазки skin pack
God, I love the
его богу вот люблю
options re,
варианты ре
but if you glue 1 cheat correctly, the types of
а если вы клей 1 чит правильно виды
Alexander Ponomarev
александр пономарев
2003 are older and have a private view of
2003 так вот старше и у частных виду
Ukraine on the euro baci, not Alexander
украины на евро baci не александром
Ben-Hur, he himself comes from km, the snail, the children,
бен-гур еще сам родом с км улитку детки
places in Ukraine, he recognizes
места в украине он узнает
this is rich in cool people saints so
этом богата клевых людей святым так и
2003 lesson is visible ledges scab her
2003 уроку видно выступов паршина ее
fishing I won’t go astray as renshaw also had
рыбачье не собьюсь как реншоу также была
songs here ruslana in 2004 and gave heat
песни сюда руслана в 2004 и дала жару
greenjek go then bishop
greenjek поди потом поехал епископ
omr went  on the street there at once we do
омрачен улице там разом нас багато нас
n’t have a big fight put us plus who created the
не подрачить поставьте плюс кто создал
song with a frequent earlier revolution, the mind of
при частом раньше революцию песню разум
us is rich, don’t overdo
нас багато над не подолати
it
у
at such you all
на такие вы все
youngsters became big
малолетки большого стал
in 2004 and the terms in the toastmaster
в 2004 и сроки в тамада
and okay and let's think about the
а окей и давайте задумаемся
chain with chat roulette so
цепочка с чат-рулетке так
likes
лайки лайки
balalaika likes last up to 6 from
балалайке так длится до 6 от лайки
likes, at least 20 likes are enough and we
достаточно хотя бы 20 лайков и поддаемся
succumb to chat roulette rustams, and since we all know them,
рустамов чат-рулетке а поскольку им все
we
знаем
rejoice, I interceded so the Russian
радуемся як я заступался так русский
character of the point was, having dropped this mugu flake
персонаж точки было выпав это мугу флаке
out, I can lay experience with you
наружу мoгу заложить опыта вами
for your experience with her, and if
за ваш это опыт у нее а если
Dawkins
перекрутится докинз одну
will be twisted one for you, we will be Vitaly Solansky Kirov
за вас буду мы виталия солански кирова
named after 40 already
имени уже 40
I’m in the course of just the third in youth
я в ходе просто третего по молодёжному
it looks like
выглядит так
this for roulette
это за рулетку
and Lexus past
да лексуса мимо
max star is magnificent riad about commentary and you
макс звезда пышен рияд про комменту и ты
walked Russia life you don’t group and
шел руси жизни вы ей не группировки и
sound and ooo base
звуком и ооо база
and also  I knew the car of the year calling ours already a year
а еще авто года зова наши знал уже году
before
до
I know
знаю
from the stick vigilantly we will try the film, it’s
от палочки зорко попробуем фильм можно
possible to work there until the test water
будала там стоит работу до по тесту вода
would be there all sorts of barrels of the type succumb to the
бы там всякие с бочин типа поддаются
ball
шаром
t  so let's give up, give in to their
так давайте поступаемся поддаемся их
knocking shafts of sustanon
стук валы сустанон
[music]
[музыка]
like this in general a day and
такой бы вообще в день и
let's immediately share
давайте сразу пай
right away try to enter you or
сразу попробуйте входа ты или прочую и
something else and rusty so we don't just surrender ourselves to the type of saludos on sticks,
мы на палочках не просто отдаемся вида
you can serve records there by
салюдос вы можете подавать там записи by
in silence with a shark and so on buns  we on
в тиши акулой так вот на булочках мы на
we repent to
мы каемся
analyze it later zoom you and
проанализировать это позже зуме ты и
logic psychologists in one q here I think and
логику психологи в один q вот я думает и
kim others
ким прочие
install
установ
fools spa
дураки спа
yura voloshchuk who you write by profession
юра волощук кто вы по профессии пишет
means you my videos I hope in my videos I
значит вы мои ролики надеюсь я в своих
often
роликах часто выказав
show Igoryans hang themselves there and victory day right away
удавиться там игорян и день победы сразу
mid it's there my colleague and I drive to be
мид это там я с коллегой диск
located
располагаться
profession by the
профессии
way we write under
кстати пишем под
sergeevna voice I don't know the voice on
сергеевна голосе я не знаю голос на
filling
наполняем
so here I am and the couch expert
так вот я и диванный эксперт
come on
давай
good afternoon I ask people from Russia
добрый добрый день я у людей из россии
how do you feel about the war in
спрашиваю как вы относитесь к войне в
ukraine
украине
attributed again, that is, do you think that
отнести снова то есть вы считаете что
incorrectly, our Putin has been looking for a captivity of the crust for a long time,
неправильно нашу путин долго искала
as a citizen they think that it is
корки как гражданин считают что
negative
отрицательно
who else to dig and another hypostasis you are not
кто еще копать и другой ипостаси вы не
negative,
отрицательный
I am a pood  I'm confused go I'm confused by the
я за пуд я я запутан пойти мне запутали
authorities of Russia and Ukraine, let
власти россии и украины меня за давайте
's try now to get confused two ticks of a
сейчас попробуем раз путаться два тик
kind and some say that you know what
вида и одни говорят что вот знаете что
needs to be done others say while saying
это надо сделать другие говорят а говоря
and others say that people died there
а другие говорят что там людей погибло
once and and many corpses are brought to us like
раз и и к нам привозят много трупов как
as if how, how to be, look
как как будто как ну как быть смотрите
here is my opinion, it seems like it’s necessary not
вот моё вроде как бы мнение так надо не
to attack another country, that is,
нападать на другую страну а то есть
for example, if Ukraine was a window, that
например если вот украина была окна вот
’s just Andrey you by here I have
как раз андрея вас by вот у меня вот
Rustam called Rustam
рустам зовут рустам
[music]
[музыка]
see Andrey and what  you now do
смотрите андрей и что вы вот сделайте
what
того что
I need an ordinary ordinary person,
мне обычного рядового человека
even if not even an ordinary ordinary person, the
пускай даже не обычного рядового
charter dropped beer right now,
устав пиву щас уронил
here’s an ordinary ordinary person
вот обычная рядового человека
put on some path of truth
поставите на какой-то свой путь истины
to change something don’t look, let’s
что-то изменить не смотрите давайте
start with the fact that you are not an ordinary ordinary person
начнем с того что вы не простой рядовой
than you correctly said  a citizen,
чем вы правильно сказали вы гражданин
so a citizen, this is
так гражданин это вот
according to Hastings, by the way, he will serve Ukrainian beer,
по гастингс кстати пиво украинскую
but I delivered no beer,
подаст а а доставила пива
well, let's
нет ну давайте давайте
get it, that is, your president, on
получается вы то есть ваш президент от
your behalf, send  no troops to ukraine
вашего имени направляет войска в украину
and kill people on behalf of citizens and the
и убивают людей от имени граждан и
sian federation gets we don’t have our
сийской федерации получает нет у нас
own name not but acts he
своего имени не а действует действует он
who elected him
кто его избирал
take on when he’s
возми на когда он
already rich about personalities like here
дуже багато о персоналиях типа вот
on your behalf kill she sends these
от вашего имени убивай она посылает эти
troops to ukraine press don’t twin  on your
войска в украину жми не twin от твоего
behalf, only tobacco, if your
имени только табачный вот если ваша
president, sending troops, look like his
президент посылая войска вид своего
name, so we see his twin president, the crowns of the
имени так видим его twin президент венцы
log house, so vanilla Ossetia, you still
сруба так ванильная осетию еще вы - учит
teach, but everyone didn’t have a boom-boom
повидали зато у каждого ни бум-бум было
on a long pencil at the pineapple and hulks to
на длинный карандаш у ананаса и громадин
eat, and the chronicler number I have
поедать а летописец номер я причем
the president sent,
президент послал
do not confuse on our own, we elected him,
не путайте от своего мы его избрали но
but on his own behalf, what they take takes
он от своего имени то чем берут берет
full responsibility no who he
всю ответственность нет кого он
represents whom he crosses he
представляет кого он крестами он
is representatives of that
представителей того
Russian people
российского народа
he is a representative of the state
он представитель государства
correctly who is the main hormone in the state
правильно кто есть в государстве главный
he is his deputy and if anything they are
гормон он его заместителя и если что они
all  what kind
все эти какого
of guilt from it turns out the guilty tsar
от виноват из получается виноватый царь
and his deputies, and you are not guilty of the
и его заместители а вы не виноваты в
people in the corps, but  to him look at the frames of
корпусе народ а почему смотрите на рамки
ordinary people people
обычных народ народ
that left their people people watch
что оставил их народ народ смотрит
TV and
телевизор и ходят
go shopping go to work
по магазинам ходят на работу
here I am for example I am a trolley bus driver you
вот я например я водитель троллейбуса ты
made me a clamp
сделал мне кламп
just really start a trolley bus in this
чуть правда заводить троллейбуса в этом
wrote a
писала
muzzle that he is rudely digging a
мордоворот что он грубо копаешь
businessman then shares ordinary people and a
бизнесмен то акции простые люди и
trolley bus
троллейбуса
put a plus for someone revealed with 2 of
поставьте плюс для кого-то выявилось с 2
them a present.  sasha drive a taxi wow
ним подарочек . саша водить такси ого
just water and bulo
просто воде и було
where there was a pipe that was in the water and
где была труба что в воде и троллейбусы
put trolleybuses plus who blowing off all kinds of such a
поставьте плюс кто сдува все виды такой
profession say his face
профессии скажем лицо его персонажи швам
shouted that there it is necessary to take an
не таким голосом крикнул что там надо
interest
поинтересуемся
extract possesses
экстракт обладает
before
до
so go so
так пойдите так
I sew up is in nevada total
я зашиваться является в неваду итогу
buffer background so it is more than kps
буферный бэкграунд так она пуще кпс
try to exit such wine buv date yak I
пробуйте выхода таким вин був дата як я
shook against you vadim trolleybus
качал противо ты вадим троллейбуса
to ukraine [ __ ] on a trolleybus come
на украину [__] на троллейбусе приехать
to and look you have elected this
на и на смотрите вы избрали этого
president  you elect you pay
президента вы избираете вы платите
taxes for now not against him I love my
налоги пор не против его я люблю своего
president by basing still abysses, that
президента базированием еще пучин то
is, you continue to support his
есть вы и дальше поддерживайте его
actions you don’t go out to, for example, at a
действия вы не выходите на например на
rally, stop the killing of people in
митинге остановите убийство людей в
Ukraine, then you are responsible
украине значит вы несете ответственность
for this, my
за это
friend, and everyone will go out there,
дружочек и все выйду туда
I alone survived  who will just crush me
я один выжил кто меня просто раздавят
like a monkey, well, it seems everyone is
как мартышку ну вот кажется каждый так
sitting like that and if one if one if
сидит и если один если один если
you know, you know you’re a pro, she’s
знаешь ты знаешь ты же профи она тебя
already
уже [__]
[ __ ] you up, you know, and it’s such a damn thing that
пропесочили ты знаешь и такое [__] что
when there are 400 thousand of them, anyway,
когда будет 400 тысяч таких все равно
[ __ ] bend over,
нахуй нагнут бля ть
look, the Russian Russian troops entered the
смотрите русские русские войска зашли
world of sleep, but the Ukrainians even went out there on an
мир сон но украинцы вышли даже там на
armored personnel carrier or on a tank with a flag, so what
бтр вылазили или на танк флагом ну и что
and not to be afraid,
и не бояться
I heard that the two met when,
я слышал что встретились две когда еще
well, not really, since I had all these
ну не совсем так как у меня было все эти
lawsuits against the prayer of the division, but this is [ __ ], but
иски к молитве дивизии но это пиздежь но
our boys say if our boys
наши пацаны говорят если наши пацаны
say it means normal, then it’s
говорят значит нормальный значит это
true, they
правда
just didn’t want to put forward there
просто так не хотели выдвигать чтобы там
because of
из-за
from the
из
Kherson division so that no one after the
херсонской дивизии чтобы никого не по
king then, well, your
короля потом ну ваши
two brigade commanders met, 2 not brigade commanders,
встретились два комбрига 2 не комбрига
two battalion commanders from Kherson,
два командира батальона из херсона и
and how do you know this, where do you get the
и вы вот это откуда знаете вот откуда вы
news from, well, according to the
берете новости ну вот по
herald of the herald, you are because of the heat and
глашатай глаша ты из-за жары и
well, two two two met  the battalion
ну вот встретились два два батальона
shook hands
пожали друг другу руки
hugged and parted in different directions
обнялись и разошлись в разные стороны
this is where he is
это где он
well it was not shown anywhere before
ну это не было до этого нигде не было
sorry you are used to the actor
показано извините вы привыкли что актер
showing on the phone  and here the real
показывать по телефону а тут настоящие
Russian
русские мужики
Slavic men dispersed, I think that this is
славянские разошлись я считаю что это
generally where did you find out from where
вообще откуда вы вот это узнали откуда
did you find out so
вы узнали так вот
they say they say who brewed the
говорят говорят кто заварил
trolleybus they say that when you go
троллейбусе говорят вот когда вы едете
on the way they say the trolleybus they say
на пути говорят троллейбусе говорят
but it was a long time ago only just if
но это был давно лишь просто если
stability and grief know this is true
стабильность и горя знать это правда
ok, look, and this is how you think when
окей смотрите а вот так считаете когда
ukraine defeats russia, so russia
украина победит россию так вот россия
will pay reparations to ukraine to
будет выплачивать украине репарации для
compensate for damage
возмещения ущерба
from destroyed and people were killed there, and
из разрушены и там дома убиты люди так и
russia will pay a fine conditionally
россия будет платить штраф условно
saying yes to their ukraine, it turns out this
говоря да их украине получается эти
money will be taken from your
деньги будут забираться из вашей
salary also here you think  it’s
зарплаты также вот вы считаете это
right, it’s right, he
правильно будет
’s asked him a battle
вот задал ему батальная
wrong, I’ll still be
неправильно буду еще
reparations from Russia when they
репарации россии когда
pay and Ukraine from the Ukrainian
выплачивают и украине из украинской
sea will be for a brother, including eat and
морем будут за брата из том числе съем и
pay his gifts, he will train and the version of
зарплаты его подарки он обучить и версия
hips is this and you are strong for
гаразд бедра у этой и вы сильны к на
such information as
такую информацию как
living up to
жить до
a twin  birth year core Wednesday many
а twin зарождение года ядру среда много
things wool will pay reparations
вещей шерсть будет выплачивать репарации
fact
фактически брат звездных платы за европу
he knows everything such a salary knows the
он знает все такая зарплата знает
salary for europe he knows their si knows
зарплату он их си знает
that for a fee part will be
что за плату часть будет
for rebuilding ukraine
на отстройку украины потому
because i'm not a troll but why
что я не тролль а почему
because the title will not be why you
потому что звание будет не на почему вы
look export with countries on behalf of and
смотритесь вывоз со странами от имени и
you at home  sovskie that
вас дома совские что
well, ukraine seems to win within its framework,
ну украина кажется победить своих рамках
trump will win against its framework,
трамп победит победить своих рамках
it will take its land, but
своих рамках она заберет свою землю но
it will never be compared with russia, never,
с россия не сравнятся никогда никогда ни
in any case, look at russia
в коем случае не на смотрите россия
will pay reparations, then more herbs
будет выплачивать репарации то еще трав
and so relatively speaking so that you
и так условно говоря чтобы вам было
can understand these  fines will be taken from the
понятно то эти штрафы будут браться из
budget, that is, you will receive fewer payments,
бюджета то есть вам будет меньше выплат
so the
так на зарплату
salary will be received from the salary, and the
получает от зарплата будет уходить и чем
more and booklet
больше и букле ни
in nothing, and I don’t want to quarrel with anyone and
в чем и я не хочу ни с кем ссориться и с
I want to respect you, I’m dumping you,
вами хочу что же я вас уважаю сваливаю
well, a smart educated person here  and I
ну умный человек образованный вот и я
also
тоже
worked for 17 years in law enforcement
17 лет отработал в правоохранительных
agencies,
органах
and who wrote the moment there,
а кто там писавший момент
Vitaly Kis, guessed both in the water and guessed the
виталий кись угадал и в воде и угадала
alcohol, you remind me met in the
спирт вы напомните встречала в
hour  at-roulette Vitaliy delivery honestly
чат-рулетке виталий поставка все чесно
met everything,
встречала
but I’m forged like a freak of a ski track
но я че кованый по уродок лыжней
police tpr water and a trolley bus
полицейские тпр воде и троллейбуса
lazaro usa history here I think you
лазаро сша буда история вот я думаю что
know
знаете
well
ну
somehow I don’t know I never
как-нибудь я не знаю вот никогда не
thought that like this everything
думал что вот так вот все вот за
will never come back  I never thought, but in
вернётся никогда не думал никогда не а в
which expressive finger worked or
каких выразительные работали палец или
in the internal troops, look how
во внутренних войсках вот смотрите как
you think then who should compensate for
вы думаете тогда кто должен возмещать
this damage there destroyed houses
вот этот ущерб там разрушенные дома
crippled destinies America Americans and
искалеченные судьбы америка американцы а
why because they
почему потому что они
supplied you
снабжали вас
with weapons that destroy you,
уничтожающим у оружием
that is, it turns out Russia attacked
то есть получается россия напала на
Ukraine bombed  cities should pay
украину разбомбила города платить должны
Americans, so my
американца так
friend, you don’t understand it yourself, everyone
дружочек ты сам-то не понимать это все
understands how old you are forty
понимают вот сколько тебе лет сорок
forty, well, don’t look at me in the eyes
сорок ну вот не 37 посмотри мне в глаза
inside
внутри
this is a war of Americans with Russia, this is
это же война американцев с россией это
not a war, and I
не война и мне и
don’t really, I’m very sorry what the
не действительно я очень жаль то что
[ __ ]  this is happening in ukraine it’s a
[__] это происходит на украине очень
pity
жаль [__]
it could have happened in kazakhstan and
это могло произойти в казахстане и в
belarus so they wanted
беларуси вот они хотели беларуси сначала
belarus to do it first  to lie, but they didn’t
это сделать но у них не получилось
succeed,
получилось
look at you, I got to the bottom, got
посмотрите у вас вот докопался докопался
to the bottom of your record shop, so when I
до вашей пластинку shop вот я когда
meet people who have an opinion there and
встречаю людей которые там мнение а
then they talk and starting with the flesh of America,
потом говорищь и начиная с плоть америка
that is, it turns out you probably also
то есть получается вы наверно тоже там
count there too, here the NATO base could not be
считать уж тут база нато нельзя было
allowed to be here  biolaboratories
допускать что тут биолаборатории
american before
американский до
this one didn’t beat laboratories here in general it’s
этот не била лаборатории тут вообще
simply
просто
impossible to be allowed to our borders to
нельзя допускать к нашим границам к
Russian NATO here and everything
российским нато вот и все
again, on the other hand, we have blues well,
же с другой стороны у нас стоят сины ну
or not at all, but soon they will be from
или вообще не надо но скоро будут от
fishing balta room balta alaska the
рыбалка балте комната балте аляска
last one I would give you
последний буду я бы дал вам
but he said cool words to
но и любых сказал классные слова на
me for this, they can quickly attract it,
меня за это могут притянуть быстро
it’s not a prison, just
это получается не тюрьма просто
some HIV words and you’ll say that
кое-какие слова вич и будешь говорить то
you are already a
ты уже
former policeman, you know that,
бывший полицейский да знаешь то
but for example, it turns out and fired
а вот например получается то и уволит
sometimes you shoot expensive blessings, look
иногда снимаешь дорогие благин посмотри
it turns out according to your  america
это получается по вашему америка должна
will have to compensate ukraine for the damage from
будет возмещать украине ущерб так от
this war,
этой войны
yes, somehow in my head it doesn’t fit
вот у меня как-то в голове не вяжется
bombing ro  Russia should pay America
бомбит россия оплатить должна америка
pays in the first place, these all all the garbage,
платит во первых вот эти все всю хуйню
here it is for you and the
вот это вот вам и
censorship, as if politically
цензурная словно них политичес
many miles and a billion dollars of its budget
много миль и миллиардный свой бюджет
dumps you dumps
сваливает вам сваливает
it works it works it works
он работает он работает работает
for the Russian troops and then
по российским войскам и тогда
sooner or later
рано или поздно заканчиваются
everything ends up and just look it turns out  just
все и смотрите просто получается вот
imagine you have an apartment,
представьте у вас есть квартира
I come knocked down and start smashing
я прихожу сбитой и начинаю вас громить
everything in the apartment so you other
все в квартире так вам других вам другой
neighbor gives you a gas canister that you defended yourself from
сосед дает газовый баллончик что вы от
me like that but a
меня защитились так но
couple of
парочку
examples were like this and it turns out that the
как примеры были так вот и получается
museum shows an analogy to him, so
музей ему аналогию показываете поэтому
count you on the project there  according to the
на проекта там сосчитай вас данным
welding, I give him a gas cylinder to
сварка я ему даю газовый баллон
pay for the damage, not the one who beat the
оплатить должен за ущерб не тот кто бил
beaten one who gave the gas cartridges
битая тот кто давал газовые баллончики
for protection, so it turns
для защиты так получается
out that the countries my friend have
масштабе что страны дружочек
good teeth [ __ ] you have never been in the war, were
хорошие зубы [__] ты ни разу на войне
not vegetables and were
не был дать не был ни был овощные и были
in the war a vase  bulls
на войне вазу быки
galoshes won’t show you can’t see it
галошки не покажете вы не видно по силам
because ordinary Russians have bad teeth
потому что обычного русских плохие зубы
you are good  Yes, he was well chosen in the war,
вас хорошие да он хорош выбрали на войне
good, I was in the war with peas,
хороший я был на войне с горошками
normal, I’m not dentists, I understand
нормальные я не стоматологи разбираюсь
the war from Ukraine, not but what kind of war
на войне с украины не но она какой войне
were the
были
Chechen war, so it was in the 90s
чеченской войне так это же было в 90-х
how much you were in 2004, and then it
вам сколько было в 2004 и то это уже
’s still  war is in this
все еще война это в этом
just like a policeman
просто как полицейский
eliminating militants,
устранение боевиков а
but look at Kadyrov, so Kadyrov, he
вот смотрите кадыров так кадыров он же
was a militant, he killed
был боевиком убивал русски
Russians na'vi Chechen days, because it was already
na'vi дни чеченским потому что уже
time, and the vin buv
времени было так а вин був
inner sands of the van and there are police
внутренних песках ван и там полицейские
functions
функции
like the most Yak NKVD st in the 50s hands  on
как самый як нквд ст в 50ых руках на
acc not in the west of ukraine,
акке не на западе украины
both cleaned it up ok licking and
оба зачищал это ок лизни и
you gave this peck, now it’s equal to doing
этом клевки ты дали вот равен занимается
dreams on the blue n-sky supports, and
сны синим н-ского опорах а
now even if I honestly still
теперь я даже если честно еду сих пор
don’t understand this, well, what happens
этого не понимаю ну что получается
now Kadyrov kills
теперь кадыров убивает в мариуполе
Russian speakers in Mariupol and Russians turns out in
русскоязычных и русских получается во
the name of Russia,
имя россии
well, there
ну там
he created several regiments, several companies, and
создал несколько полков несколько рот и
so on, they die
так далее они гибнут
on the territory of Ukraine, it’s just a mystery to me,
на территории украины просто для меня
it turns out a bunch of Russian
это загадка получается куча русских
guys died who is better than my Cheche  ntsy
парней умирала кто лучше чем мой чеченцы
will fight on ign, I handed them out,
буду сражаться на ign я протянул их их
we’ll try a-data than to wash Yakovitch, and who
попробуем a-data чем отмыть якович а кто
is the character for nationality to teach
же персонаж за национальности научить
his version of yours, listened and listened to his
свою версию о твоих слушал и слушала его
rusts, and you latvian introduced
рустам да и вас latvian представился
himself as Aven for nationality from letting loose and the
авен за национальность от напустить и
version,
версия
yes, I’m them by type of people  and I already read that
да я их по типажу людей и уже читала то
they are brought up as warriors,
их воспитывают как воинов
look, look, it turns out
смотрите смотрите получается русские
that the Russians died a lot of Russians in order
очень много русских умирала для того
for
чтобы
Kadyrov to become the
кадыров стал
head of the republic, so it turns out,
главой республики так получается
yes, no, your locals were a militant,
да нет местные ваш был боевиком
well, you know,
ну ну ты же знаешь
matchsticks, it
спичечные
just turns out why these guys
просто получается за что же эти ребята
died, he killed the Russians and he  became the
умирали он убивал русских и он стал
main in the republic, his putin gives him an order
главным в республике его путин орден ему
from imagine the guy killed Russian
из представляешь парень убивал русских
guys and
ребят а
now he is given the order by the hero of Russia it’s
ему теперь орден дают герой россии
sad it’s
печально это
sad that something is wrong here
печально что то здесь не так
somewhere deceives us you know how they tell
где-то нас обманывает знаешь как говорят
you to tell how you saw the video but
вам рассказывать как ты видел видео но
your
ваш
disobedient or there for  of
ослушники или там за париком
course, they tortured our guys with a wig in locks,
наших ребят в замочки конечно
well, in short, they threw it like that and
ну короче закинули вот как и
scream and ask who the [ __ ] is with you
кричат и спрашивает кто там [__] у тебя
help
помоги
rashid enter the usual bend you
рашид входим обычных подогнуть you
[music]
[музыка]
to buy a command by a russian
to buy команду русским человеком
person and it
да и
turns out in russia the chechens up to manages the
получается в россии чеченцы до управляет
russians now not and they are clearing the chechen chechens by the
русскими теперь не и они прочищаются
permian
чеченские чеченцы пермскими
orbital about this I didn’t quite understand the
орбитальные про это не совсем понял
chechen republic is in the composition
чеченская республика находится в составе
but they are russians not russians they are
но они россиянина не русские они
russians i
россияне я
not Russian citizens either, not Russians, not Russian either,
не граждане русские тоже не русские тоже
but who by nationality I am a
не русский а кто по национальности я
Tatar, the
татарин
answer is
разгадка
Vitaliy Chukchi in annual to win faces
виталий чукча в годовых to win лица
Vitaliy Kovalchuk, sellers of wines, water and
виталий ковальчук продавцы вин воде и
going to what is there since the 6th year and issued in the
что там с 6 года и выдавшую in the toren
toren, Vitaliy Pinchuk
года виталий пинчук
knew I already put a plus  who believes
знал я уже так поставьте плюс кто верит
in the details of the ideal year for the second time,
в детали идеального в года вторые разы
amin, all the same, the nearest vitalik chews the
амин все таки ближайший виталик жует
chat roulette chat and
бачив чат рулетки и
give it like that and then one goal Astrakhan
дать так и затем один гол астраханский
Russian
русский
[music]
[музыка]
these wolves dress them up with the
эти волки одевалки они с
Chechens in general, they can’t be confused
чеченцы вообще ни с чем не перепутать ни
with anything, they can’t be compared with anything  these are real warriors and
с чем не сравнить это настоящие воины а
Russians are not wars and
русские не войны и
Russians, but
русские но
I’ll say
скажу
why
чем
it’s unrealistic wars
он нереально войны
Russians thump in the army
русские бухают в армии
don’t drink worms at all  l came to me during the
вообще не пьют вормил ко мне во время в
army in the army before the war while line
армии в армии до войны время строчки
hazing went
дедовщина ездил
I served in
я служил
2004 2006
2004 2006
for all the services I drank one walkie-talkie then
за все службы выпил одними рацию то
before the
перед дембелем
demobilization she was a good officer they drank well they were
она сочи был хороший офицер они пили
good really a good officer
ну хорошие действительно хороший офицер
and there is not for this among
и там не за этим среди
here look how you are  do you think it turns out how the
вот смотри как ты думаешь получается чем
war will end boucle don’t know how I
закончится война букле не не знаю чем
’ll end up from what you think I
закончу от как ты думаешь я
’m even afraid to even think I think that
я даже боюсь даже подумать я думаю что
it will drag on for many years do you
это затянется на много лет как ты
think the krin will completely win to
думаешь у крина полностью выиграет
liberate its territories of the Donetsk and
освободить свои территории донецкой и
Luhansk regions on the stock exchange involuntarily
луганской области на бирже невольно
why
почему
than
чем
for example you  two months ago I thought that
например ты два месяца назад думал что
Ukraine was capable of stopping the Russian army at all, the
украина способна вообще остановить
risk was just that they threw
русскую армию риск просто вам накидали
weapons at you like hell, but
оружие [__] а
in fact it was a
самом-то деле
good offensive, it wasn’t just a good
хорошего наступления это не было просто
case, Lord Jesus, the currency was
господи случая господи исусе валюта не
n’t worn like that, Lord Jesus, are you
было носить такой господи иисусе ты
something
что-то
like
такое
that and what did we have  thousands of your dead
а что это был у нас тысячи убитых ваших
if he takes everything from the twilight
если у твайлайт он
except for this, but this is not yet a
заберет всю кроме а вот это пока не
war, this is so specially
война это так специально
not [ __ ] your Ukraine from us then  did
не на хую ваши украины от нам то ли
I earn money to steal her [ __ ] and
заработав я же украсть ее [__] и и
everything is fine let's Rustam drag on and the
все хорошо давай рустаму затянулась и
conversation has already been a lot of time two
разговор уже времени много прошло два
this beer has cooled down already or not
этом пиво остыло уже или не
flour and well I want to say the
муки и хорошо хочу сказать
types of move and chauvin we are not finally zara
виды хода и шовен мы не напоследок zara
capturing to say but to honor with our weight
захватив сказать но почтить своим весом
and said dug  and I
и говорила вырыл и я же каждого я
said goodbye to everyone and I’ll kill them, you
прощалась и убью оборвала
know, I want to say, I didn’t know at
знаешь я хочу сказать вот я не знал в
that moment you would visit, I didn’t guess that
той момент на посетят вы я не угадал что
he wouldn’t want to say any of someone’s and we
он не захочет сказать никакого чьих-то и
’ll guess Ashby a bit, she’s a vitalik,
загадаем эшби толик она виталик
you’ll write Rustam at least their riddles
напишешь рустам хоть их загадок и
and Vince gave  for 1, well,
у винса дал за 1 ну
let's drink for this oil
выпьем за данное масло
in the position,
на позиции
how
как
did you
приколе ты давай чем ты где-то в колене
start to take
участвовала в школьные годы а
it?  so they persuaded them with
врага говорить уговорили значит и ими
serious things to say such a cool
серьезными вещами такую такую прикольную
joke from the end, it’s just that I know
шутку сказал с конца вот просто я знаешь
about nexia, and maybe even when to joke the
про nexia а может ещё когда пошутить
evening I’ll repeat it again, you’ll be
вечер еще раз повторю сдам будешь
damn real  but it’s a joke the second time it
блин реально но шутка второй раз она уже
doesn’t sound like that anymore, it’s somehow cool,
так не звучит надо как-то прикольно этим
you can give it up even cooler, in fact
можешь еще круче по сути
give up, but look what is equal and
сдавайтесь а вот смотри что есть равно а
what if we don’t give up what will happen
что если не сдадимся что будет
you will come to Ukraine on a trolley bus you didn’t
ты на троллейбусе приедешь в украину не
support you didn’t support the war and now
поддерживал не поддержал войну а теперь
you say surrender  and that means you
говоришь сдавать и значит ты
support, drank and started supporting
поддерживаешь попил и начал поддерживать
all the
всех
neutrals a little bit a little bit
нейтральных чуть чуть чуть чуть
and you look and don’t support the
поговорить и смотришь а не поддерживает
war, that is, you let the channel down to this, you
войну то есть к этому подвел канале ты
started talking to russia and so it
начала общаться россию и так деле она
attacked ukraine how should
напала на украину как я должен
i how can i already russia you were born
как я могу я уже россии ты родился
ukraine  if your country attacked my
украине если твоя страна напала на мою
country you should burn dry vova
страну ты должен гореть сушат вова
president partner how are we two larvae
президенте партнер как мы две личинки
such poses to each other 1 forest each
такие позы друг другу 1 лесного друг
other and all
друга и все
for the sake of everything what is the difference can you be larvae in russia
ради все в чем разница может вы в россии
so and we are citizens in ukraine we
личинки так а мы в украине гражданами мы
make a politician
делаем политик
we are in russian  federations are not only
мы в российской федерации не только
larvae we are a cell of citizens
личинки мы ячейка граждан
it is also
это еще
not accurate to look at and you are proud
это не точно просмотреть и ты гордишься
you were learning you are proud of the country in
ты была учатся гордишься страной в
which you are a larva
которой ты личинка
who  nothing is affected by
которые ни на что не влияет
anyone's credere hotels katich, and a cell and a
ничей credere hotels катич и а ячейка и
larva, then one cell with a larva, a
личинка то одна ячейка с личинкой
larva of candles,
личинка свечей
fawned a lot too much,
много лебезил лишнего
okay, let's go there, in fact,
окей хорошо давай иди там на самом деле
I love Ukraine, but like you
я и украину люблю любишь но типа войну
support the war, it turns out, it doesn't support,
поддерживаешь получается не поддерживает
I'm confused in my testimony, you  apparently
я запутался в своих показаниях ты видно
show it to law enforcement and bite
покажи в правоохранительной и закусываем
their testimony but I won’t get
их показаний зато мне не будет
such a thing from the major yes everything is fine let’s hold on
такого от майора да все хорошо давай
I 6 because I understood
я 6 ведь в комнатах понял
the hair in
волосы 12 blind работа по анализу в этом
the rooms 12
не будет айвен мы валим про умывался
blind  we raise
и мы там займитесь стали мы поднимаем
it before the trip there, he just has 5
занимал до похода там у него просто 5
seat fugitives, or maybe it’s just the season or the
сидушка беглецы а можно просто сезон или
washbasin became hot, the view is equal
умывальником жарко стало вид равно
to the right, and well, about politics, sand
вправо и ну про политику песок
ablution to do
омовение сделать так
so and not 2 x trim the miracle of Kadyrov’s that
так и не 2 x trim чудо кадыровцы что
falls into pilaf, change it right away
попадает в плов меняйте сразу
and let’s
так и давайте
eat at the same time
заодно питания в
heading without google this both players and
рубрике без гугла этой оба игрока и
good
хорошем
food on the geography of ukraine
питании по географии украины
these areas are lake svityaz
эти области находится озеро свитязь
teach these areas of ukraine  there is
учить эти области украины находится
lake svityaz
озеро свитязь
with our guests their
с наши гости их
advaita version of the media
адвайты версии сми
who indulged in this wiki on your dunk
кто предался данного вики на ваш дунк
area there is lake svityaz
области находится озеро свитязь
so plebeian 6c
так плебей 6c
famine kent action volyn region
голод кент акция волынская область
and any lubeck didn’t smoke right and
а любую любеке не правильно ли курил и
so we had versions of
так у нас был версии там черкасска
cherkassk blueberries and ivano-frankivsk to fool  to
черника и ivano-frankivsk охмурить к
daala, throwing off the beating, I saw the
даалы бьющийся скинуть повидала был и
tskad action 1 with a guide of their Ukrainian universities,
цкад акция 1 с гидом их украинских вузов
so junk and kia of the bazaar could go out in
так мог рухлядь и kia базара выйти в
ukraine, so there are three such things, both signs, then
украине так такие штуки три оба знака то
the singers are great in ukraine, still
и певички велике в украине еще
come across an accident with the Russians, tell me where
попадаться дтп с россиянами скажи а где
is Svityaz lake and you don’t  will be of
находится озеро свитязь а вы не будет из
us and was not crumpled from Voloshin along and
нас и не было смято из волошиной по и
Ukraine with him, tell me, I know where Baikal
украины с ним скажи я знаю где байкал
finds an act of y and
находит актом у и
geography and nature of a prominent edge for
географии и природу видного краю
so long, good
так долго благо
for today, let's close ours according to
на сегодня о давайте закрываем наш по
yours,
вашему выполнял
as
как
here, for experience, you are no more than graves on
вот же на опыт вы не бильше могил на
rusi c jumps after hundreds in horror name and you
руси c прыгает ведь сотки в ужасе name и
can see cool 40 kind of pictures you respect this
видно круто 40 вид фотки уважаешь это
kind top on the mind and 79
добрая топ на разум и 79 widgetkit после
widgetkit  if string and in
таких начинал мысли string и в
Novosibirsk passes an arc of 8,800 sq.
новосибирскую проходит дуга на 8 800 кв
so we have cheerful flowers of great and
так у нас веселыми цветки великих и
assembly in moscow and
сборки в москве и
neutral k1 visa since 200 34
нейтральными k1 visa так как 200 34
votes
голоса булан окей
bulan ok ton i put extreme put at
тонна я поставила экстрима поставте хотя
least leave it will be like a track yes harm you
бы покиньте будет like трек да вреда вы
come to visit only  what you are watching you
заходите в гости только что наблюдает вы
don’t leave and it seems kind to let him
не уходит и кажется добрый дать ему
remember came to the stream than turned on the
запоминать пришли на стрим чем включила
video became like it good afternoon at
видос стал это like it добрый день у
krypton who didn’t subscribe to the
криптона кто не подписался на канал
subscriber’s channel and every 2200 tank we
подписчица и каждый бачек 2200 мы
climb on the commandant’s wand we’ll
взбираемся на комендантском палочки
look in the ass and pull a life hack not over the
заглянем попку и натащить лайфхак не над
novel alive a note  on the cheek, I
романом заживо нотку на по щеке на
’m tired of someone for some not 102 sun age 3, I
устану кто за некую не 102 sun age 3
’m re-reading the whole
обовязково перечитываю хотим всю
geography, so about wild Miyazaki, glued in
географию так о диких миязаки вклеен в
on the ship on the stream, then there’s little
на судне на стриме богатов то мало
comment and olaf throw them people there writes
комменту и олаф киньте им люди там пишет
and a Calvinist, he’s also drag xii heads of the
и кальвинист он же натащить xii головы
place and May 3  musya ukrainian and
места и 3 мая муся украинец и цена
jabber price can semi extremely
jabber можете полу крайне
[music]
[музыка]